你头发有点脏乱了
It's getting a little messy for you.
我准备退休了
Getting ready for retirement.
不用遵守仪容规定了
Relaxing the grooming standards.
想去当个水管工
Thinking about becoming a plumber,
牧羊人什么的
a sheepherder, or something.
你现在可不是在牧羊 亚伯拉罕
You ain't herding sheep now, Abraham.
搞清楚状况
Eyes on the prize.
太对了
Damn right.
这才是我的好姑娘
That's my girl.
也许我会让你刮掉我全身的毛
Maybe I'll let you shave me down all over,
像海豚一样光溜溜
dolphin-smooth.
我今晚帮你刮
I'll cut it for you tonight.
好 女士
Yes, ma'am.
也许罗西塔也可以帮你修剪一下
Hey, maybe Rosita can give you a trim while she's at it.
你背后的头发有点长了
Party's getting a little long in the back.
莫非这是你力量的源泉吗?
Or is it your source of power?
我最近不会屠杀狮子
I ain't slaying a lion anytime soon.
我可不会打赌说我自己会
I wouldn't be placing any wagers on seeing me
用一块驴腮骨杀掉一千个非利士人
dispatch a thousand Philistines with the jawbone of an ass.
你就只打算拯救世界 对吧？
Oh, so you'll just settle on saving the world, right?
是啊
Yeah.
怎么了？
What's up?
- 是昨晚的事吗？- 不是
- Last night? - Nope.
是的 昨晚和明天的事
Yes, that and tomorrow.
我在想那个牧师
And I'm thinking about that preacher,
他做的事
what he did.
也许他们就在我们后面
Maybe they're just behind us.
也许达里尔和卡萝尔回来了
Maybe Daryl and Carol came back.
也许他们拿了地图 找到了车
Maybe they took the map, found some cars,
就在路上
and they're just down the road.
他们会赶上来的
They'll catch up.
我们在为他们开道
We're clearing the way for them.
多长时间才能奏效？
How long will it be?
在你到达终端 做你该做的事后？
After you get on that terminal and do what you have to do?
取决于许多因素
Depends on a number of factors
包括世界范围内标靶位置附近的感染密度
including density of the infected around target sites worldwide.
等等 标靶位置？
Wait, target sites?
你是说导弹吗？
Are you talking about missiles?
那是机密内容
That's classified.
我还以为你不再保密了
I thought we were over that.
如果我们都活下去了呢？
What if we all live?
那时候秘密就重要了吗？
The secrets will matter then?
也许
They might.
总之 一切恢复正常的速度
Anyway, the speed with which things normalize
取决于很多因素
depend on a number of factors
包括全球气候模式
including worldwide weather patterns,
对此的建模并没有假设
which were modeled without the assumption
汽车 飞机 船只和火车
that cars, planes, boats, and trains
会这么长时间不向大气中排放碳氢化合物
wouldn't be pouring hydrocarbons into the atmosphere this long.
这让通过空气传播的病原体充满了变数
Changed the game quite a bit when it comes to air-transmissible pathogens.
为什么留这个发型？
Why the hair?
因为我喜欢
Because I like it.
而且不许任何人剪我的头发
And no one is takin' scissor or clipper to it anytime soon.
你听到了吗 埃斯皮诺萨小姐？
Do you hear me, Miss Espinoza?
是的 听得很清楚
Yes, loud and clear.
你们可以随便笑
You all can laugh all you want.
没人在取笑你啦
No one was making fun.
我遇见的最聪明的人碰巧喜欢我的发型
The smartest man I ever met happened to love my hair.
我之前的老板 布鲁克斯·埃利斯
My old boss, T. Brooks Ellis,
人类基因组计划的主管
the director of the Human Genome Project.
他说我的发型让我看起来像是 我引用
He said my hair made me look like, and I quote,
"一个有趣的人"
"A fun guy,"
我确实是
which I am.
我只不过不是参孙而已
I just ain't Samson.
《行尸走肉》
艾伦…
Ellen...
艾伦
Ellen!
尤金
Eugene!
尤金 你没事吧？
Eugene, are you okay?
那个传教士…
The preacher...
别无选择
didn't see another way out.
坚持住？
You hold on, okay?
其他人呢 都没事吧？
Everyone else, you all right?
- 没事 - 没事
- Yeah. - Yes.
- 引擎着火了 我们得赶快离开 - 我知道
- The engine's on fire. We gotta get out of here. - I know.
好 我俩先走 把它们击退
All right, you and I go first, knock them back,
给玛姬和罗西塔开路
clear the way for Maggie and Rosita to get out,
然后我们一起解决它们 行吗？
then we all start hitting them, okay?
- 行 - 好的 我们会活着的
- Yeah. - All right. We'll do it live.
- 塔拉？ - 什么事？
- Tara? - Yeah?
你掩护尤金 等安全了再出来
You cover Eugene. You come out when it's clear.
- 好的 - 等我信号
- Okay. - On my go!
上
Go!
快点 我知道这可怖之极
Come on. I know it sucks and it's scary,
- 但你必须鼓起勇气 - 这不是我能控制的
- but it's time to be brave. - It isn't voluntary.
你能的 不然你只有死路一条
It is, when you're screwed either way.
你必须抉择 拯救他人
So you cut through the choice that might help somebody.
来吧
Come on.
我就在你身后
I'm right behind you.
看看尤金有没有受伤
Check Eugene, see if he's hurt.
我没事 就一点擦伤
I'm fine. Just cuts and dings is all.
去看看
Check him!
- 这是你的血吗？- 是
- Is that your blood? - Yeah.
伤口又裂开了
Damn thing opened again.
我发誓 伤口非常小
I swear, the cuts are finer than frog's hair.
只是容易流血
They're just big bleeders.
急救箱在巴士里
First aid kit's in the bus.
我去看看有什么能用的
I'll see what we have.
我们不能停下 必须继续前进
We're not stopping. We're rolling on.
在路上再找一辆车
We'll find another vehicle down the road.
任务不变
The mission hasn't changed.
我唱句反调 没别的意思…
Devil's advocate, nothing more...
我们出了严重的车祸
we smashed to a stop hard.
而且路上一直在挪开障碍
We spent a lot of time rolling things out of the road.
- 这里离教堂只有15英里… - 不
- The church is just 15 miles back that way... - No.
不能停下 也不走回头路
We don't stop. We don't go back.
这是战争 撤退就是战败
We're at war, and retreat means we lose.
道路险阻 计划多舛
The road fights back, the plan gets jacked.
这又怎样
You all know that.
我们必须克服一切 因为我们没有选择
Now, we will get through this because we have to.
每一步都有未知的危险
Every direction is a question.
但我们决不后退
We don't go back!
你还好吧？
Hey, hey, hey. You okay?
我简直不能更好
I am fit as a damn fiddle.
我们会跟着你
We are going with you.
一切由你决定
You are calling this thing.
但我必须要确认你没问题
I just need to know you're good.
失败都是这样开始的
This is how things stop.
我现在承担不起失败 世界也承担不起
I can't afford that right now. The world can't afford it.
听着 出车祸了我很受挫
Listen, I took a pretty hard shot to the sack with that crash.
看到巴士毁了 我压力很大 也很沮丧
I am stressed and depressed to see that ride die,
但是如果你说我们继续走
but if you say we're rolling on,
我就没问题
I'm good.
我们继续走
We're rolling on.
这种伤抹点泥土 走走就没事了
I'm gonna rub some dirt on it and walk it off.
我们会像以前一样 在路上找到
We'll find what we need like we always have...
- 需要的东西 - 好的
- on the way. - Okay.
我可不会乱抹什么泥土
I'm not rubbing dirt on anything.
或许我们可以找些自行车
Maybe we can find some bikes.
自行车不会起火
Bikes don't burn.
走吧
All right.
好
Right.
尤金 你在干什么？
Eugene, what are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
我们走
Let's go.
艾伦
Ellen!
艾？
Ell...?
艾伦？
Ellen?
艾伦
Ellen.
我们走
Let's go.
我去搜索一下
I'm gonna take a sweep.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢什么？
For what?
谢谢你能来
For showing up.
虽说做了点交易才把你弄来 但是…
It took a little horse trading to get you here,but...
现在我看明白了
it's plain as potatoes to me now.
你懂
You get it.
车祸后你本可以说明理由
Coulda lit out after the crash,
然后离开 但你留下了
made a case, but you stayed.
我约定过
I made a deal.
是啊 但也可以反悔
Yeah, you coulda broke it.
我又能怎么样呢？
What was I gonna do?
你今晚要把那东西收起来吗？
You gonna put that thing away tonight?
你的手呢？
How about that?
不包起来吗？
You gonna wrap that up?
不 我要让它透透气
No, I'm gonna let it get some air.
昨晚在教堂 手都刮花了
Got cut up pretty ugly last night back at the church.
是啊
Yeah.
能活到现在的人都很强
Gotten to the point where everyone alive is strong now.
我们别无选择
We have to be.
强者要么与他人并肩作战 互相利用
You're either strong and they can help you so you help them or...
要么因为太强而被杀
you're strong and they can kill ya.
所以你必须杀了他们
So you gotta kill them.
你必须杀了他们…
You gotta kill them and...
我想说杀人并非易事
I want to say it's never easy.
但事实并非如此
That's not the truth.
如今最简单的事莫过于此了
It's the easiest thing in the world now.
世界会改变的 对吗？
The world's gonna change, right?
那当然了
You're damn right it's gonna.
快去休息吧
You'd better turn in.
你晚点还要放哨呢
You've got late watch.
行
Yeah.
我要先去来一发
I really need some ass first.
你没必要告诉我 不过 挺好的
Didn't need to know that, but, cool.
亚伯拉罕
Abraham!
他又在那儿看呢
He's watching again.
就在那边的自助区
Over there in the self-help section.
"自助"
"Self-help."
宝贝 别担心
Don't worry about him, baby.
他没什么危害
He's harmless.
- 我已经到了 - 来吧
- I'm already there. - Come on.
老兄
Dude.
我坦白 我是在看他们
Cards on the table, I was watching them.
是啊 我看到了
Yeah, I saw that.
我相信他们知道我偶尔会看
I believe they know I catch an eyeful on occasion,
这不是他们的癖好 也不是我的
which isn't to say it's their thing. It's not mine either.
只是因为我喜欢女人
It's just that I enjoy the female form
而这样做既不会害人
and I consider this a victimless crime
还能让我得到安慰和消遣
that provides both comfort and distraction.
也许… 也许我们可以换个地方说
Maybe, uh... maybe we can move on from here.
我刚刚在找你 想和你道谢
I was looking for you to say thank you
你在巴士那里掩护了我
for having my back at the bus.
你救了我一命
You saved my life.
我觉得不算吧
Don't know about that.
你确实救了我一命
You did.
假如我真救了你
Well, if I did, then,
那也是因为你给我提供了机会
you provided the context for me doing so.
- 什么 - 不管怎样我都死路一条
- What? - I was screwed either way,
所以我选择拯救他人
so I went with the choice that helped someone.
我以为这话很老套 但却发现是真的
I thought it trite, but it turned out to be true.
多亏了你
Point to you.
你本来就有这个力量
You have this.
假如你之前没有 现在也有了
Even if you didn't before, you do.
听着 我也是一样的
Look, I'm... I'm the same way.
你知道你自己可以的
You know you can do this.
你听到我刚刚说的话了吗？
Uh, did you hear what I just said?
巴士翻车都怪我
The bus crashed because of me.
- 不是的 - 就是的
- No, it didn't. - Yes, it did.
我把玻璃渣放进了燃油管路里
I put crushed glass in the fuel line.
是我之前在教堂里找到的灯泡弄的
Light bulbs I found in the church.
那辆车
The vehicle
本应该在上路前就坏掉
should've failed before it ever got to the road.
你差点害死我们
You would've killed us.
本来不应该像这样坏掉的 完全不应该
It wasn't supposed to go down like that, not hardly, not half.
玻璃渣不应该弄坏
The glass wasn't supposed to
火花塞旁边的燃油管路
wear out the fuel line next to the spark plugs.
我们运气太差了
We fully pulled the short straw on that one.
搞什么啊？你为什么这么做？
What the hell? Why did you do that?
尤金
Eugene,
你为什么… 尤金？
why did... Eugene?
你为什么这么做？
Why did you do that?
回答我
Answer me.
我赞同善意的谎言
I appreciate the positive affirmations
和对某些事视而不见
and looking the other way on the perversion,
但是根据我的经验
but I know empirically
我知道我绝不可能独自生存下去
and definitively I cannot survive on my own.
- 我不行 - 所以你就弄坏了巴士吗？
- I cannot. - So you killed the bus?
假如我不能治愈这场瘟疫
If I don't cure the disease,
不能拯救世界 我就毫无价值了
if I don't save the world, I have no value.
事情不是这样的
That's not how it works.
假如我不能解决这一切
If I don't fix things,
你们绝对不会把我带在身边
there's no way you people would keep me around,
和我分享资源 甚至是保护我
share resources, even protect me.
我们当然会的
Of course we would.
我们是朋友啊
We're friends.
我们要互相照应的 就这么简单
We have each other's backs. That's it.
事情就应该是这样的
That's how it works.
别告诉别人你做了什么
Don't tell anyone else what you did.
我会为你保守秘密 我们会继续前进
I'll keep your secret and we'll keep going.
你知道自己搞砸了
You know you messed up.
你在努力 但是 老兄
You're trying, but, dude,
你不能再这么做了
you can't do something like that again.
我不会了
I won't.
你和我们绑在一起了
You're stuck with us.
就像我们和你绑在一起一样
Just like we're stuck with you,
无论如何都是如此
no matter what.
我不知道自己为什么会告诉你
I don't know why I told you.
我知道
I do.
欢迎加入人类 混蛋
Welcome to the human race, asshole.
走吧 很晚了
Come on. It's getting late.
你在想他们吗？
You thinking about them?
是啊
Yeah.
我感觉好内疚
I feel guilty.
也许这算我们…
Maybe we get to have...
在书店地板上的小假期
little vacations on bookstore floors.
我们现在不在那里
We're not back there anymore.
我们为其它的事而活
We're living for something else.
而他们现在还不能这样
And they don't get to right now.
我们今天差点死了
We did almost die today.
而且我们没车
And we don't have a car.
还得从厕所取水喝
And we're drinking toilet water.
但是这样的感觉依然很好
It just feels really good having this...
因为过去不再重要
because it's not about what was.
昨晚不再重要
Not last night.
重要的是未来
It's all about what's gonna be.
别为此感到内疚
Don't feel guilty about that.
艾伦
Ellen.
现在安全了
We're safe now.
我阻止了他们
I stopped them.
你们现在不必害怕了
You don't have to be scared now.
没事了
It's okay.
没有感染
It's not infected.
你还偷偷去过护士学校吗？
You been going to nursing school on the sly?
是罗杰和帕姆教我的
Roger and Pam taught me.
我觉得今天我们应该留在这里
I think we should stay here today.
不行
No.
你准备在这里读书吗？
You got some reading you need to catch up on?
我们昨天侥幸没事
We got lucky yesterday.
但我们都受伤了 特别是你
But we're all banged up, you especially.
我们经历过更糟糕的事
We've been through worse.
我们得继续走
We keep moving.
也许我们总是被迫停下
Maybe we always wind up stopping
是因为我们总是没准备好就上路
because we never start at 100%.
去华盛顿的路上 我们浪费的每一分钟
Every minute we waste getting him to Washington,
都有人死掉
people are dying.
你以为我不懂吗？
You think I don't understand that?
经历了这一切之后？
After everything?
听着 我可是真的想让大家抵达目的地的
You see, I want us to actually get there.
不 你想让我们闲坐着
No, you want us to sit around.
你想让我们停下
You want us to stop.
这座城镇还不赖
This town isn't in bad shape.
这间书店甚至还完好
This store wasn't even touched.
这可以成为不错的基地
We could make a good base here.
我们可以花最后一天时间找些补给
We could spend one last day doing a sweep for supplies.
我们边走边找
We'll sweep as we go.
从休斯顿开始就是这么做的 现在不能停下
We've done it since Houston. We're not stopping now.
你们听到女士的话了
You heard the lady.
我们往北走
We're taking it north.
厕所里没水了
We tapped out the toilet.
布劳德河在西边八公里的地方
Broad River is five miles west.
找到车之前 我们至少要到那里补给一下
At the very least, we stock up there before we find wheels.
其实有辆车
We got a vehicle.
碰巧…
And it just so happens...
车上装了五百加仑水
it's got 500 gallons of water on it.
我们也该走运一次了
About time things started going our way!
拜托
Come on.
就一次
Just once.
就不能走运一次吗
One damn time.
我们会找到别的车的
We'll find another ride.
如果镇子里有能用的车 我们早就看到了
If there was a ride worth a shit in this town, we'd have seen it.
这辆车被用来撞过行尸
This thing's done some crowd clearing.
正好阻塞了进气口
Right up into the intake.
那就意味着
Which means we've got an
空气过滤器塞满了该死的尸骸
air filter filled with damn human remains.
这世界上每一个该死的小角落
And there is no damned corner on this damned Earth
都被破坏的面目全非了
that has not been dicked hard beyond all damned recognition.
亚伯拉罕？
Abraham?
干嘛？
What?
这是散热器的通风口
That feeds the radiator.
引擎的进气口在车顶上
The intake for the engine is actually on the roof.
塔拉 玛姬
Tara, Maggie!
就不能走运一次
One damn time!
- 就一次 - 亚伯拉罕 等等
- One damn time! - Abraham, just wait!
后面还有更多
There's more from the back!
我参加过七个乡郡庆典
I been to eight county fairs
和一个山羊竞技比赛
and one goat rodeo.
都没这个让人开眼界
I never seen anything like that.
书店旁边有家慈善商店
There was a Goodwill over there by the bookstore.
那里残破不堪 但可能会有些补给品
It's pretty blown up, but there might be some supplies,
一些干燥的衣服
some dry clothes, maybe?
没必要
Not necessary.
我两三下就能清理好进气口
I can clear that intake in two shakes.
然后引擎就能吸入空气
Then the engine will get some wind
我们也就能兜风了
and so will we.
你们会吹干的
You'll air-dry.
我们继续走
We roll on.
(内有病人 让他们死)
咋的？
What?
太扯淡了
This shit is screwed up!
AJ？
AJ?
贝卡？
Becca?
(别来找我们)
艾伦？
Ellen?
艾伦
Ellen!
(赫伯特·乔治·威尔斯 《未来的模样》)
我知道你为什么留这个发型
I know why you have the haircut.
我说了 因为我喜欢
I told you, it's 'cause I like it.
我相信 我也很喜欢
I believe that. I like it, too.
我觉得你喜欢是有原因的
I think you like it for a reason.
你不是别人以为的那种人
You're not the person people think you are.
你想向他们展示真实的自己
You want 'em to know who you are.
不懂你在说什么
Not following you.
如果你不留这种长发
If you didn't have that mullet,
你就和其他科学家一样了
you'd probably be like everybody else in the labs.
但是你跟别人不一样
But you're not like everybody else.
如果别人处在你的位置上
I think a lot of people in your position
可能早就放弃了
probably woulda given up,
但你没有
but you didn't.
我这一路上… 有很多人…
There were people... a lot of them along the way...
他们确保了我不放弃
they made sure I didn't give up.
根本不是我的功劳
It wasn't me remotely.
是你的功劳
It was.
这一切都多亏了你
You started this thing.
你和参孙不一样 他头脑不清
And you're not like Samson. He was kind of a mess.
不懂你在说什么
Not following you.
他的故事是…
Well, his story goes...
有一天一只狮子袭击了他
that one day when a lion attacked him,
上帝给了他力量 将狮子撕成两半
God gave him strength and he tore it apart.
之后他又独自回去
Then he goes back one day, he's by himself,
看到蜜蜂在遗骸上造了蜂窝
and he sees that bees have made a hive in the carcass.
然后他就把这个谜语讲给世人
So later he tells this riddle to people.
"吃的从吃者出来
"Out of the eater, something to eat.
甜的从强者出来"
Out of the strong, something sweet."
我一直在想
And I always thought,
这是关于他自己的生活经历
"How the hell are people supposed to know
别人怎么能猜得出
the answer when it's just about his own life?
答案只在他自己的脑袋里
When the only place the answer is is in his own head?"
这是什么味道？
Whoa, what the hell is that?
什么？
What?
起风了 你马上就能闻到了
Wind's picking up. You're about to smell it.
那是什么啊？
What is that?
不管是什么在发臭
Whatever's making that stench,
反正不是什么好东西
it ain't nothing nice.
我们不能停下
We're not stopping.
我们已经停下了
Uh, we're stopped.
走吧 我们得走了
Let's go. We gotta go.
我不会投降的
Yeah. I will not lie down.
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
我不会屈服的
I will not abase.
亚伯拉罕 咱们离开这里吧
Abraham, let's get out of here.
我不会认输的
I will not give up the ship.
等等
Hold up.
- 我们该走了 - 不行
- We gotta go. - No.
不 不能走
No, we don't.
它们听不见也看不见咱们
They can't hear us and they can't see us.
离得很远
Not from here.
我们没事
We're fine.
是啊 这就是所谓的没事
Yeah, this is the definition of "Fine."
我们需要地图 肯定有路能绕过去
We need the map. There's gotta be a detour.
我才不干
I'm not doing it.
我们从休斯顿到乔治亚一路都在绕道
We detoured and detoured and detoured from Houston to Georgia.
我再也不这么干了
I'm not playing that game anymore.
我们没法直接这么穿过去好吗？
We are not going through this, okay?
这是不可能的
It isn't gonna happen.
A门后面是狂风暴雨
You got a shitstorm behind door A
B门后面是暴雨狂风
and a storm of shit behind door B.
如果够幸运 顶多碰到行尸或者卡车被击毁
If you're lucky, it's walkers or a shot-up truck.
但早晚会被逼入绝境
But sooner or later you get cornered.
你只能待在原地 最后自相残杀
You wind up staying and you wind up killing.
我们不会回头 也不能回头
We don't go back. We can't go back.
我不是说要回头
I'm not talking about going back.
- 只是往南走几里 - 不行
- Just south a few miles. - No.
我们已经因为内脏堵住了空气过滤器
We already hit a full stop because of an air filter
而止步了一次
compromised by innards.
类似情况会再次发生的
That will happen again.
那就再用水管收拾它们一次
Then we'll hit them with the hose.
水箱里没水了 亚伯拉罕
The tank is empty, Abraham.
如果我们把油门踩到底…
If we floor it...
我们还是会撞上行尸 它们还是会拖慢我们的速度
We still hit them, they still slow us down,
之后我们就会被困住
and then they stop us.
我不是说要直穿过去
I'm not saying we just go straight.
这条路就是直穿过去的
That's the way the road goes.
- 亚伯拉罕 - 我们可以穿过去的
- Abraham! - We can get through!
我知道
I know it!
那意味着我们不能往南走
And that means we are not going south,
不能绕路 也不能回头
going around, or going back!
不
No.
他们说得对
They're right.
亚伯拉罕
Hey, Abraham.
- 你在干什么 住手 - 放开他
- What are you doing? Stop. - Let go of him.
我不会让你这么做的
I'm not gonna let you do this.
- 不 你会的 - 快住手
- Yes, you are. - Hey, hey, stop.
- 滚开 - 你完了 你完了
- Get out. - Hey, you are done! You're done!
- 别这样 别这样 - 住手
- Do not! Do not! - Stop!
我跟你说过了 别碰我 别碰我
I told you, you do not touch me! You do not touch me!
亚伯拉罕
Abraham!
我不是科学家
I'm not a scientist!
我撒谎了 我不是科学家
I lied. I'm not a scientist.
我不知道要如何阻止这一切
I don't know how to stop it.
我不是科学家
I'm not a scientist.
你就是科学家啊 我见识过你做的事情了
You are a scientist. I've seen the things that you can do.
我只是知道一些东西
I just know things.
你只是知道一些东西？
You just... "Know things"?
我知道我比大多数人聪明
I know I'm smarter than most people,
我知道我很擅长撒谎
I know I'm a very good liar,
而且我需要去华盛顿
and I know I needed to get to DC.
为什么？
Why?
因为我相信在那里
Because I do believe that locale
生存的可能性最大
holds the strongest possibility for survival,
而我想要生存下去
and I wanted to survive.
如果我能骗一些人带我去 那么
If I could cheat some people into taking me there, well,
我会对他们说 我这也是在帮他们
I just reasoned that I'd be doin' them a solid, too,
考虑到休斯顿的危险环境和现状
considering the perilous state of the city of Houston, the state of everything.
为了帮你走到这里 很多人都死了
People died trying to get you here.
我知道…
I'm aware of that...
史蒂芬妮 沃伦 帕姆
Stephanie, Warren, Pam,
雷克斯 罗杰 乔塞亚 德克和约瑟芬
Rex, Roger, Josiah, Dirk, and Josephine.
还有鲍勃
And Bob.
我们离得越近 我越害怕
You see, I lost my nerve as we grew closer,
因为我是个懦夫…
for I am a coward...
一想到抵达目的地后
and the reality of getting to our destination
我就必须揭示真相
and disclosing the truth of the matter
令我非常恐惧
became some truly frightening shit.
我想方设法减慢我们的速度
I took it upon myself to slow our roll.
抽时间来进行安排 这样等我们到了以后…
Find time to finesse things so then when we got there...
但是在这一刻
But at this moment,
我终于意识到我别无选择了
I fully realize there are no longer any agreeable options.
不管怎样我都是死路一条
I was screwed either way.
我还撒谎说布鲁克斯·埃利斯喜欢我的发型
I also lied about T. Brooks Ellis liking my hair.
我不认识布鲁克斯·埃利斯
I do not know T. Brooks Ellis.
但是我读过他的一本书
But I did read one of his books,
他看起来不像那种
and he seemed like the type of guy
会介意田纳西大礼帽长发的人
that wouldn't blink twice at a Tennessee Top Hat.
再说一次…
Again...
我比你们聪明
I am smarter than you.
你们也许想把我丢在这里…
Now, you may want to leave me here...
- 喂 - 住手
- Hey! Hey! - Hey, come on!
别碰他
Get off of him!
- 天呐 - 别
- Oh, my God. - No.
尤金？
Eugene?
起来 看着我
Get up. Look at me.
天呐
Oh, my God.
天呐 尤金 你还好吗？
Oh, God. Eugene, are you there?
尤金
Eugene!
醒醒
Come on!
艾伦
Ellen.
救救我
Help me!
救命 救救我
Help! Help me!
求你救救我
Help me, please!
它们来了 干掉它们
It's them. Get them!
干掉它们
Get them. Get them.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢
我觉得它们的速度变快了
I think... I think they're getting faster.
等等
Wait!
等等我
Wait up!
站住
Stop!
- 你不能走 - 为什么？
- You can't leave! - Why?
我身负着一项非常重要的任务
I have a very important mission.